where we have the repository and the
system
that is talking about anybody comes and
you advance somebody forward
the system
the sister can identify that
it's made of these details
in anybody
but this is something
was
analysis and after that what are the
execution strategies we just made into
that
pre-learning process very important
religious is is also not a static sleep
on changing in terms of that
i will give i will share with you about
the slides it does not require take a
photograph
so regular interaction with the game
should be averaging this can design and
implement control
situation as the requirement it gets
um
[Music]
is very very important
to control
one other case study
[Music]
you know these photographs were pasted
in the right person
we found the page
however you should confirm the percent
test drive
the same as follows
[Music]
you know
um
so this is so interesting
here we did a lot of work where we
approached
[Music]
it is uh
online basis
so that is one of the one of the factors
it is supporting us
now this online factor is supporting
each other's companies irb gic
uh this paribas ccp
so these are the difference part
so it is very very important in terms of
financial company where
we have more that means
sorry for that
okay
major for difference
[Music]
of
and that is not an expectation of the
issues companies
i'll just say to you that these are the
things that we can differentiate people
see there are soldiers everywhere
we become captain when we do different
things
[Music]
okay
so
how we work in terms of
product view that claims to company
trigger
how it works
so few triggers uh
let me
uh red flag of talking about combination
of below parameters go toward policy
breaking close fortunately 15 days this
is not a static again i'm telling you
credit score uh we defined in such a way
that we get the
cases it falls and then we integrated
when when aims come to the company it
integrated in such a way that it shows
us the numbers
score based directly model social media
analytics and subject figures these are
the
these are the
changes i'm talking about
it's very very important
i just explained to you red flags
that's simple and very very simple
types of red flags
tell about what is the meaning of words
[Music]
so we should take it as
mismatch is
subjectivity
[Music]
who visits
in some other insurance company and now
he is coming to our policy over here
yes yes
it will help you to think more
absolutely so that is not there in fact
it is
[Music]
working on that part
we are
we are working on the existing planes
and again we are talking about the past
closed cases and the existing policy
also we started and we are taking calls
on that path that is that is a good
trigger
the pressure is on time
yeah so in my second tool i would like
to talk on uh
forensic
is one of the
important factors that everybody is
aware that
earlier came used to get some statement
from this person to that person
earlier
today we talk about the policy is so
much development and this
is not a fixed thing foreign
keep on doing changes
um
digital mode of interest in what we are
doing
okay it was only the manual thing today
after location
there is a gap there is no information
between today we have the details up to
that level okay on the ground level we
can have the details
there are so many analytics we can do on
basis of this
so many things real time we can get into
this there is a
real-time connection on the field
and we have the screen today where we
can see coming
that is
[Music]
is what investigation is what we are
talking about
investigation has a detailed recovery
system and examination
that is what investigation we should
know what is investing you are talking
about
carefully search or examine to describe
facts ask yourself who what when where
and why and what small video is there
actually if you send me a video
oh
um
come on
[Music]
you know
after the video
the planning predictions
it is not that something we got we need
to and now we get to stage things and
then we can contribute somewhere it is
not just community today we start to
invest something but after 10 steps that
is not what we wanted something
different we get there are so many
stories for example harushi matter case
and if you talk about running how it
started
coming up so these are the investigation
investigation is not a big setup that we
can determine at the time of beginning
it is that one please travel along to
the past and see company americans
that's okay
is
[Music]
that is very very important
and that way in conclusion where this
this this vehicle recovered
you know somewhere
but see the profile of the doctors
and uh
this is what
type of god they they created and it is
not so simple to interrogate certain
people when they have the influence
it is not simple that we can do some
statements it is not
that simple that whatever
it's the fact that also that in a
insurance company we need to show
attribute that situation uh you know for
this situation is very very difficult
for you
because those set of people will come to
the company to get the policy to get the
name and it is happening if you can't
believe in the property and fire claims
we have seen the multiplication of cross
where people bought the place
and they got the policies and they
they manipulated things and they claimed
the folio documents and the different
intentions
and that is what is happening the
situation based
this is a
stolen
[Music]
you know that type of video they started
so one of the
video is checked by one of the police
officers and he just called our manager
what is this case and then they share
the details and that that matter that
person already deal with this person who
did that this
happened to be this
vehicle
then what we did we
this person the police person he
you know returned all the documents the
back complement details atm and the
transaction
the maximum transaction where it is
happening we plotted that okay
and
to northeast today is happening now that
the vehicles are going there this is
happening by so many vehicles
expected what we recovered
from that area
so see the nexus how it stands most for
things can
build on things
this is also interesting
where
one of the uh today also you guys are
doing this part i suppose something uh
published in the newspaper
where uh some information and
somewhere you can connect that part it
also happened that one of
them papers
here see one of the news
unidentified personnel
we come to know about this part and we
come to this isolated
then we investigated and we chaired the
items for police
and the police walked on their part
and
they raided and once
they
got the vehicle
that is
this is
[Music]
they
need to
are very then